faceit.com 2013-05-01

# FaceIt - Challenge your game

### INTRODUCTION

In this Privacy Policy, which is available via a link at the bottom of the homepage play.faceit.com, "we", "us", "our" and the “Company” means FACE IT LIMITED, as well as its affiliates on its behalf, including FACE IT SOFTWARE LLC (collectively, "FACEIT"). This Privacy Policy works hand-in-hand with the Terms and Conditions of Use (hereafter the “T&C”), which can be found here, and any terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning given in the T&C.

For the purposes of the Data protection Act 1998, the Data Controller is FACE IT LIMITED located at 2 Throgmorton Avenue, London, EC2N 2DG, United Kingdom.

This Privacy Policy applies to all "users" of the Site. This includes unregistered visitors as well as users who have registered and maintain an account on the Site. This Policy does not cover the Privacy Policies of other web sites, nor any information collected through any other website operated by third parties Each of these web sites may have a Privacy Policy that differs from ours and we urge users to check the Privacy Policies of each web site that they may visit orinteract with.

This Privacy Policy will remain in full force and effect - even if your use or participation in the Site or any particular Service, tournament or game offered through the Site terminates or ceases, or is suspended or deactivated for any reason - in order to ensure that you may easily restart gameplay at a latertime. In any case, should you continue to be an inactive player for more than four years, FACEIT will delete your personal information.

If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not participate in the Site or any of the activities or Services offered through the Site.

### COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

When you register on the Site we collect Information through the completion by the user of contact forms and surveys, and through his or her interaction with the Site (for example, which games you play, player rating information and gamestatistics). Users may provide other information about themselves, in addition to the mandatory Personal Information (hereafter “Voluntary Information"). Voluntary Information include, but are not limited to, information collected when they use features on the Site, such as messages, chats, the "Invite Your Friends " feature, or when they contact Customer Support. For example, we collect names and e-mail addresses of the user's friends when the user uses the "Invite Your Friends" feature on the Site. We may also require you to provide additional personal information, such as your name, an avatar, age and address (via a copy of your driver's license or utility bill), for the purpose of verifying your identity, including your address, in order to participate in our Site. As stated in the T&C, address and identity verification are a mandatory part of the withdrawal process.

A. Types of Information

We collect two types of information from you when you visit the Site: non personally identifiable information (hereafter "Non-Personal Information"); and personally identifiable information (hereafter "PersonalInformation").

(i) Non-Personal Information

Certain technical information related to your visit to the Site may be automatically recorded. This information is anonymous and does not identify you personally. Non-Personal Information includes, but is not limited to: the Internet domain for your Internet service provider; the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer accessing the Site; the address of the last webpage that you visited prior to clicking through to the Site; the browser used and the type of computer operating system that your computer is using; information about your computer hardware; the date and time that you visited the Site; and a record of which pages you viewed while you were visiting the Site. Other information such as demographic information, which does not identify an individual, is also considered Non-Personal Information. Gaming Information (described below) is also considered Non- Personal Information.

(ii) Personal Information

When you register for a free user account (a "Free Account"), you consent to our collection of Personal Information including your email address, for the purpose of validating your address, and in order to market upcoming game tournaments and email to reminders and promotions regarding the activity on the platform. If you choose to create an account which will allow you to enter cash games and tournaments (a "Cash Account"), you will be required to provide additional information such as (a) your name, date of birth and mailing address, for the purpose of ensuring that you are permitted to create an account based upon your age and where you reside, and that you comply with the T&Cs, and (b) gender, should you agree to provide same, for the purpose of FACEIT better understanding the demographics of our players. If you choose to make a deposit into your Cash Account, you will also be required to provide information relevant to your payment method (for example your credit card number and expiry date).

As noted above, the Site also provide you with certain ways to voluntarily give us your Personal Information. You may also use the features of the Site to invite others to create Free Accounts or Cash Accounts. We may also collect Personal Information about you if you choose to send us an email message, which contains such information using links contained on the Site. You may also disclose Personal Information when you post content with such Personal Information on the Site or when you contact our Customer Support representatives via live chat or email. Certain information about your activity on the Site is not itselfPersonal Information (for example, information about your game play preferences) but may be linked to your account information. For example, the following information ("Gaming Information") is publicly displayed on the Site and, provided it doesn't identify you personally, shall not be considered Personal Information:

  * your Username or Alias
  * your Skill Ratings
  * your friends on FACEIT
  * your ranking (if any)
  * your scores in games and tournaments
  * your User Profile and statistics
  * your gaming preferences or your personal motto
  * summary of your gaming activity on the Site
  * summary of your gaming activity outside the Site
  * winnings from games and tournaments
  * any personal information you chose to disclose in a chat window

We may include footage of gameplay in promotional materials such as trailers which may be displayed on the Site, or on website run by other parties including those of our marketing partners. For example, we may display highlights, "frag of the week" or similar content. This content may also include the use of Gaming Information.

We also collect Personal Information to investigate complaints of cheating or behavior that we believe may be contrary to our T&C, including the Code of Conduct. This may include screenshots of players' computer desktops or footage of in-game play.

Inaddition to collecting Personal Information directly from visitors to the Site, we may also collect Personal Information from third parties such as marketing partners to which permission has been granted to share that information with us.

Facebook Connect

When you register with us through the Site, we will ask you for Personal Information. Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, age, country of residence and email address. You can register to join FACEIT via the Site or by logging into your account with certain third-party social networking sites ("SNS") (i.e., Facebook) via our Site. If you decide to create your Account by logging into a SNS via the Site, we will extract the Personal Information you have provided to the SNS (such as your "real" name, email address and other information you make publicly available via the SNS) from the account you have with such SNS and use that information to create your Account; the information we extract may depend on the privacy settings you have with the SNS. If you are not currently registered as a Member and you click on "Register with Facebook", you will first be asked to enter your Facebook credentials and then be given the option to register to FACEIT. Byusing Facebook Connect, you are allowing FACEIT to access your Facebook account information for the purpose of completing your registration, and you are agreeing to the Facebook Terms of Use regarding your use of the Service viaFacebook.

B. Cookies

Cookies are small text files that a website can write to your computer. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. We use cookies to identify you and allow you to log in once to our web site and search or post without having to log in again and again. Cookies are also used by our affiliates or links to identify you as a User of FACEIT.

As with many major websites, the Site uses cookies. We use Cookies to recognize you when you return to the Site and personalize your settings and preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you wish, you can change your browser settings either to notify you when you have received a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. FACEIT does not use Cookies in order to store information such as your credit card number. This Privacy Policy onlycovers the use of Cookies by FACE IT LIMITED. It does not cover the use of Cookies by any other 3rd-party or advertisers.
